练习 1-20：可变重音。注意下面这个句子的意思如何
Exercise 1-20. Variable Stress. Notice how the meaning of the following sentence
随着每次改变重音模式而变化。你现在应该开始感觉到
changes each time we change the stress pattern. You should be starting to feel in
自己能掌控句子了。第一，你想要什么？这是这个句子最常见的
control of your sentences now. 1. What would you like? This is the most common
版本，只是在简单询问信息。第二，你
version of the sentence and it's just a simple request for information. 2. What
想要什么？这是从一群人中单独点出某个人。第三，你
would you like? This is to single out an individual from a group. 3. What would you
想要什么？你们一直在讨论他可能喜欢哪些东西，而你想
like? You have been discussing the kinds of things that he might like and you want
确定他的具体愿望。既然你提到了，那你想要什么？
to determine his specific desires. Now that you mention it, what would you like?
或者，他已经拒绝了好几样东西，你有点恼火地问：如果你不
Or he has rejected several things and a little exasperated you ask, if you don't
想要这些，那你想要什么？第四，你想要什么？你没听清，
want any of these, what would you like? 4. What would you like? You didn't hear and
想让说话者再说一遍。或者你无法相信自己刚刚听到的话。
you'd like the speaker to repeat herself. Or you can't believe what you just heard.
芦笋上要草莓酱？你想要什么？重复这四个句子。
strawberry jam on my asparagus? What would you like? Repeat the four sentences.